[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 16, "question": "What's the appropriate punishment for this guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 17, "answer": "Death.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Why is it that both the president and the man who wants to be president are saying nothing about guns?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, the first thing is, do they have an obligation to say something about guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Why do so many Americans not feel angry enough to demand further gun control?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNPS", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, I would take it one step further.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Is that a natural place to start with this debate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, it has been a tradition of and it's enshrined in our Constitution, the Second Amendment, the right to bear arms.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "So what are we going to do, stop trying to fight terrorists?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What is your personal interpretation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Well, my --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What do you think the founding fathers intended?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I wasn't there but we have a mechanism under our Constitution that the founding fathers put in to answer exactly that question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "If I wanted to buy an assault weapon and a load of ammunition on the Internet, for example, and I lived in New York, even with the laws that you have, and they're more stringent than many places in America, if you got anywhere stopping me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "You can't stop everything but you can stop most of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, my own thing is if you look at where these attacks have occurred, there's one common factor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "Who stops this happening?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, that's the reason I brought up the point that I did before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "EX", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "But presumably you would accept if there were no guns at all in America there would be no gun crime, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "There'd be no gun crime but there'll be other types of crime.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Do you accept that America has the worst incidents of gun murders of any of what they call the civilized world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "No, I don't think that's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "They are not true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "No, I mean, factually, it's not true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "But it is, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "No, it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.K.", "United States"]}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "How do you say you don't have a particular problem here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "No, look, the murder rate right now -- or in the U.K. is low compared to the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 375, "question": "How many murders there in 1900?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "EX", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Two murders in London --", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1900"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "At what point does your premise, more guns, less crime, look ridiculous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RBR", "NNS", ",", "RBR", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["National Rifle Association"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Well, we just heard the worst kind of junk science that's being pushed by the most extreme lobby group in the United States, the National Rifle Association, which if it had its way, there would be no restrictions at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "OK, you want me to answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "Do you understand what the difference between a semi- automatic and automatic weapon is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Answer my question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "Why does anybody need to have a gun that can fire that number of bullets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Sir, please, let me finish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "How did he fire off so many rounds then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Because he pulled the trigger many times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 458, "question": "You are quite happy for other people to go into stores and buy the same weapon with the same magazine drum that can fire off up to 100 rounds a minute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Can I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Are you done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I'm done.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Israel's not a liberty loving country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "No, Israel has very strict arms control --", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "DT", "JJS", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "-- show where you talk most of the time?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Only when the guest is talking complete nonsense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "We've tried your way for too long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "How is Faris, your daughter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "She's doing OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Just briefly tell me what the experience was like for you when this killer started?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Well, first, it was amazement that -- I thought it was just part of the movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "What were your feelings about the court appearance today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "Well, my feelings were -- I was all for hearing the charges that was going to go against him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 690, "question": "Would somebody of that age, if they are genuinely schizophrenic -- would they be in control of what they're doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 691, "answer": "Sometimes yes, sometimes not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Is there anything more that can be done to prevent this kind of incident happening again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "If you want to look at can we make movie theaters safer, you can always harden the security around these places.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Do you feel comfortable that this guy could go and buy all this ammunition, all these weapons, all this protective gear, and do so perfectly legally without anyone picking him up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "He didn't do anything to trigger anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]